Walders, Joseph; Collection mss030
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Joseph Walders Papers1949-1977
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Walders, Joseph (1948-1992)
mss030
6.98 cubic ft.
This collection contains television and film scripts, movie posters, still photographs, lobby cards, and pressbooks collected by Joseph Walders.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by Joni Browne-Walders, wife of Joseph Walders. 1992
Biographical History
Joseph Walders (1948-1992) was a writer and television producer. He wrote and produced the science television news reports for the "Mr. Wizard's World" program on Nicelodeon for 11 years. He was the author of The World's Most Challegning TV Quiz (1977) and also wrote articles for TV Guide, Popular Science, and Science Digest.
Walders received his bachelor's degree in radio and teleivsion from Syracuse Unviersity in 1971. Born in Pennsylvania, he lived in Los Angeles for many years before moving to Troy, New York.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes 151 television and film scripts, many with shooting schedules, and hand-written revisions, deletions, and annotations, 1952-1977; and 46 movie posters, 78 still photographs, 39 lobby cards, and 4 pressbooks for 68 films, many of them produced by George Pal or directed by Alfred Hitchcock, 1952-1977, all collected by Joseph Walders. Emphasis is on science fiction, fantasy, adventure, light comedy, mystery, and intrigue. Alfred Hitchcock Presents, The Fugitive, I Spy, The Invaders, and Science Fiction Theatre comprise two-thirds of the scripts collected by Walders.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is arranged into two series: Television and Film Scripts and Film Posters and Stills. Both are arranged alphabetically.
Literature; Television--Production and direction; Motion picture plays; Screenplays; shooting scripts; Photographs; Posters; Walders, Joseph (1948-1992); Hitchcock, Alfred, 1899-1980; Pal, George
- Television and Film Scripts, 1952-1977; 1; 3.44 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains television and film scripts from the 1950s, 1960s, and 1970s collected by Joseph Walders. The majority of scripts are from the television programs Alfred Hitchcock Presents, I Spy, and Science Fiction Theatre.
  - Alfred Hitchcock Hour, The: "Jar, The", 1963 October 10 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Bull in a China Shop", 1957 December 10 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Crackpot", 1956 August 31 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Cream of the Jest, The", 1956 December 7 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Crocodile Case, The", 1958 April 9 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Dontt Interrupt", 1958 May 27 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - Alfred Hitcicock Presents: "Mr. Blanchard's Secret", 1956 July 26 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Mr. Cinderella", 1956 September 14 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Nightmare in 4-D", 1956 August 27 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Restless Corpse, The", 1957 February 27 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Rose Garden, The", 1956 August 1 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: "Three Dreams of Mr. Findlater, The", 1957 January 25 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - Bat Masterson: "Cattle and Canes", 1959 November 19 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 13)
  - Big Town: "Shoplifter, The", 1953 June 1 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 14)
  - Bob Newhart Show, The: "Birth of a Salesman", 1976 January 13 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 15)
  - Bob Newhart Show, The: "Bob's Change of Life", 1977 July 12 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 16)
  - Cannon: "Devil's Playground", 1971 October 24 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 17)
  - Captain Z-Ro: "Oxygen", 1953 August 15 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 18)
  - Case of the Dangerous Robin, The: "Man in the Shadows", 1961 February 9 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 19)
  - Cowboy in Africa: "Tomorrow on the Wind", 1967 September 7 (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 20)
  - "Daddy's Gone a-Hunting" - Feature Script, Undated (Box 1 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 21)
  - Death Valley Days: "Bill Bottle's Birthday", Undated (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - Death Valley Days: "Death in the Desert", 1965 January 15 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - Dial 999: "Barge Burglars", Undated (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - Doctor Christian: no title, 1956 October 10 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - Family Affair: "Lesson for Grown-Ups", 1968 July 10 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - Fay: "Not Another Mother's Day", Undated (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - Flipper: "Dolphins Don't Sleep Part One", 1966 April 19 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - Fugitive, The: "Detour on a Road Going Nowhere", 1964 October 10 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - Fugitive, The: "Homecoming, The", 1964 March 3 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - Fugitive, The: "Just One Road I Travel", 1964 October 23 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - Fugitive, The: "Middle of a Heat Wave", 1965 June 25 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - Fugitive, The: "Nightmare at Northoak", 1963 September 23 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - Fugitive, The: "Other Side of the Coin, The", 1966 October 17 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 13)
  - Fugitive, The: "Second Sight", 1966 May 25 (Box 2 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 14)
  - Gentle Ben: "How Wild Is Wild", 1968 July 26 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - "Goodbye Raggedy Ann" - TV Movie, 1971 June 30 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - Gunsmoke: "Time of the Jackals", 1968 May 31 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - Harrigan & Son: "Comeback, The", 1961 January 7 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - Hawaii Five-O: "Samurai", 1968 May 15 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - I Spy: "American Princess, An", 1967 June 26 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - I Spy: "Anyplace I Hang Myself is Home", 1967 July 6 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - I Spy: "Beautiful Children, The", 1967 January 17 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - I Spy: "Casanova from Carnarsie", 1966 November 22 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - I Spy: "Child Out of Time", 1966 July 12 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - I Spy: "Child Out of Time", 1966 September 4 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - I Spy: "Choice, The", 1967 June 7 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - I Spy: "Conquest of Maude Murdock, The", 1965 October 21 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 13)
  - I Spy: "Cops and Robbers", 1966 November 15 (Box 3 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 14)
  - I Spy: "Crusade to Limbo", 1965 October 8 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - I Spy: "Day Called 4 Jaguar, A", 1965 October 22 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - I Spy: "Enchanted Cottage, The", 1966 August 10 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - I Spy: "Father Abraham", 1966 April 19 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - I Spy: "Few Miles West of Nowhere, A", 1967 March 21 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - I Spy: "Get Thee to a Nunnery", 1966 August 23 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - I Spy: "Gift from Alexander, A", 1966 March 28 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - I Spy: "Happy Birthday Everybody", 1967 June 12 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - I Spy: "Honorable Assassins", 1967 January 6 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - I Spy: "Laya", 1967 February 2 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - I Spy: "Lisa", 1966 February 25 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - I Spy: "Little Boy Lost", 1966 February 11 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - I Spy: "Lori", 1966 February 7 (Box 4 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 13)
  - I Spy: "Lotus Eater, The", 1967 February 2 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - I Spy: "Medarra Block, The", 1967 February 1 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - I Spy: "My Mother The Spy", 1965 December 23 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - I Spy: "Name of the Game, The", 1967 July 7 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - I Spy: "Night Train To Madrid", 1966 December 13 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - I Spy: "Now You See Her ... Now You Don't", 1967 February 28 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - I Spy: "Oedipus at Colonus", 1967 February 6 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - I Spy: "One of Our Bombs Is Missing", 1966 April 18 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - I Spy: "One Thousand Fine", 1965 November 12 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - I Spy: "Philotimo", 1966 January 23 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - I Spy: "Pinwheel", 1967 June 7 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - I Spy: "Plains in Spain, The", 1966 August 15 (Box 5 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - I Spy: "Red Sash of Courage", 1967 February 27 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - I Spy: "Rome? Take Away Three", 1966 April 26 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - I Spy: "Room with a Rack", 1966 July 18 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - I Spy: "Seventh Captain, The", 1967 February 7 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - I Spy: "Shana", 1967 July 5 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - I Spy: Shooting schedules for various episodes, Undated (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - I Spy: "So Coldly Sweet", 1966 January 28 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - I Spy: "Sophia", 1966 April 13 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - I Spy: "Spy Business, The", 1967 July 20 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - I Spy: "Suitable for Framing", 1967 March 21 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - I Spy: "Tag, You're It", 1967 July 14 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - I Spy: "There Was a Little Girl", 1966 January 10 (Box 6 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - I Spy: "This Guy Smith", 1967 March 20 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - I Spy: "To Florence with Love", 1966 March 22 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - I Spy: "Trial by Treehouse", 1966 February 25 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - I Spy: "Trouble with Temple, The", 1966 July 12 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - I Spy: "Trouble with Temple, The", 1966 September 1 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - I Spy: "Turkish Delight", 1965 December 28 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - I Spy: "Turnabout for Traitors", 1967 August 24 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - I Spy: "You Can't Shoot an Honest Man", 1967 February 28 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - Invaders, The: "Attack", 1967 May 31 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - Invaders, The: "Attack", 1967 June 6 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - Invaders, The: "Dark Outpost", 1967 August 2 (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - Invaders, The: "Enemy, The", 1967 May (Box 7 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - Invaders, The: "Explosion of Truth" - Chapter Four, 1965 June 25 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - Invaders, The: "Innocent, The", 1967 January 13 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - Invaders, The: "Labyrinth", 1967 August 29 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - Invaders, The: "Spores, The", 1967 July 12 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - Invaders, The: "Task Force", 1967 October 16 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - Ironside: "Little Jerry Jessup", 1969 December 10 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - It's a Man's World: "Beavers and the Otters, The", 1962 February 8 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - It's About Time: "King Hec", 1966 October 27 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - Lancer: "Great Humbug, The", 1968 December 31 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - Mackenzie's Raiders: "Raid to San Rodrigo", 1958 November 24 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - Mannix: "Search for Darrell Andrews, The", 1969 December 1 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - Many Loves of Dobie Gillis: "Love Is a Science", Undated (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - Marcus Welby, M.D.: "Other Side of the Chart, The", 1969 November 28 (Box 8 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 13)
  - Meet Corliss Archer: "Corliss Plays Cupid", 1954 November 9 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - Men into Space: "From Another World", 1960 January 14 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - Name of the Game, The: "Lost One, The", 1969 August 20 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - O.K. Crackerby!: "Ol' Sam", 1965 September 3 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - Patty Duke Show, The: "This Little Patty Went to Market", 1964 September 2 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - Richard Diamond Private Detective: "Running Scared", 1959 November 20 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - Ripcord: "Log-Jam", 1961 September 11 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Breakthrough", 1956 June 25 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Clock, The", 1956 May 10 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Dead Storage", 1955 June 21 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Facsimile", 1956 August 15 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - Science Fiction Thedtre: "Girl with the Flaxen Hair, The", 1955 August 19 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Green Bomb, The", 1956 February 14 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 13)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Hastings Secret, The", 1955 July 14 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 14)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Hour of Nightmare", 1955 April 22 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 15)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Invention of Dr. March, The", 1956 June 11 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 16)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Magic Suitcase, The", 1956 August 22 (Box 9 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 17)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Marked "Danger"", 1955 April 04 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "None so Blind", 1956 September 17 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "100 Years from Now", 1956 March 30 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Second Skin", 1956 June 22 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Station M I N D", 1956 August 7 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Sun Gold", 1956 July 24 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 6)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Surgery on Channel 3", 1956 July 17 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 7)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Survival in Box Canyon", 1956 May 15 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 8)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "Value of "G", The", 1956 August 14 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 9)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "YORD", 1954 December 13 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 10)
  - Science Fiction Theatre: "YORD", 1954 December 17 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 11)
  - Sea Hunt: "Jettisoned", 1958 August 5 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 12)
  - "Secret of the Incas", 1953 August 28 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 13)
  - 14. Sky King: "Speak No Evil", 1952 January 26 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 14)
  - Target: "13th Juror, The", 1958 August 7 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 15)
  - "Tiger! Tiger!", 1968 July 29 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 16)
  - Tombstone Territory: "Frozen Assets", 1960 February 18 (Box 10 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 17)
  - Untouchables, The: "Cordial Shops, The", 1962 October 1 (Box 11 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 1)
  - Walt Disney: "Willie and the Yank Part II", 1965 February 8 (Box 11 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 2)
  - Waterfront: "Trial by Fire", 1955 January 6 (Box 11 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 3)
  - Wichita Town: "Fight for Thursday, The", 1959 June 15 (Box 11 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 4)
  - Wild Wild West, The: "Night of the Pistoleros", 1968 May 8 (Box 11 (1-Television and Film Scripts), Folder 5)
- Film Posters and Stills, 1949-1975; 2; 0.54 cubic ft.
  This series contains film posters, stills, inserts, pressbooks, and lobby cards collected by Joseph Walders. Each folder contains one poster unless otherwise stated.
  - Absent-Minded Professor, The, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 6)
  - Air Hostess, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 7)
  - Airport, 1970 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 8)
  - Airport 1975 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 9)
  - Atlantis, The Lost Continent, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 10)
  - Big Sleep, The, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 11)
  - Birds, The, 1963 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 12)
  - Boot Town, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 13)
  - Bradbury, Ray, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 14)
  - Colossus: The Forbin Project, 1970 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 15)
  - Come September, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 16)
  - Conquest of Space, 1955 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 17)
  - Creature Walks Among Us, The, 1956 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 18)
  - Crowded Sky, The, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 19)
  - Dean, James (unidentified movie), Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 20)
  - Dr. No, 1962 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 21)
  - Earthquake, 1974 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 22)
  - Errand Boy, The, 1963 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 23)
  - Fate Is the Hunter - Still, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 24)
  - Forbidden Planet, 1956 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 25)
  - Goldfinger - Still, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 26)
  - Great Ruppert, The, 1950 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 27)
  - Hellfighters, 1969 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 28)
  - High and the Mighty, The, 1954 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 29)
  - Houdini, 1952 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 30)
  - Houston Story, The, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 31)
  - In Like Flint, Undated (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 32)
  - Incredible Shrinking Man, The, 1957 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 33)
  - Invasion of the Body Snatchers, 1956 (Box 11 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 34)
  - Invisible Boy, The, 1956 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 1)
  - It Came from Beneath the Sea, 1955 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 2)
  - It Came from Outer Space, 1953 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 3)
  - Jaws - 2 Photographs, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 4)
  - Jet over the Atlantic, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 5)
  - Julie, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 6)
  - Man Who Knew Too Much, The, 1956 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 7)
  - Maracaibo, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 8)
  - Marnie, 1964 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 9)
  - Mary Poppins, 1964 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 10)
  - Mouse Factory, The, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 11)
  - Naked Jungle, The, 1953 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 12)
  - Oklahoma Crude, 1973 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 13)
  - Power, The, 1968 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 14)
  - Rear Window, 1954 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 15)
  - Revenge of the Creature, 1955 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 16)
  - Riders to the Stars, 1954 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 17)
  - Rio Bravo, 1959 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 18)
  - Saboteur, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 19)
  - Shaggy Dog, The, 1967 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 20)
  - Skyjacked - Still, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 21)
  - Strangers on a Train, 1951 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 22)
  - Tell Them Willie Boy Is Here, 1970 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 23)
  - That Touch of Mink, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 24)
  - Thing, The, 1951 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 25)
  - This Island Earth, 1955 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 26)
  - Thunder Bay, 1953 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 27)
  - Time Machine, The, 1960 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 28)
  - To Catch a Thief, 1955 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 29)
  - Topaz, 1969 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 30)
  - Torn Curtain, 1964 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 31)
  - Trouble with Harry, The, 1955 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 32)
  - Tulsa, 1949 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 33)
  - 20,060 Leagues Under the Sea, 1954 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 34)
  - Vertigo, 1958 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 35)
  - Walt Disney Studio, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 36)
  - War of the Worlds, The, 1953 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 37)
  - Watch Mr. Wizard, Undated (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 38)
  - When Worlds Collide, 1951 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 39)
  - Wonderful World of the Brothers Grimm, The, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 40)
  - World Without End, 1956 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 41)
  - Wrong Man, The, 1957 (Box 12 (2-Film Posters and Stills), Folder 42)